<resources>
    <string name="app_name">East Asian Studies</string>
    <string name="navigationDrawerOpen">Open navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="navigationDrawerClose">Close navigation Drawer</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="JapanHome">The Japanese higher education system is a very powerful tool for their national politics and culture. The Academic accomplishments of the students studying in Japan are higher and befitted the international criteria and standards. The general policy, management and administration are under the authority of the Ministry of Education.The Japanese Government has the authority to sanction the formation of all new higher education institutions, both private and public. The finances of Universities, Junior Colleges, Specialised Colleges, Graduate Schools and College of Technology come under the jurisdiction of the Ministry of Education or Monbusho. It also lays down the minimum standards for universities with regard to curriculum, facilities, qualification and number of teachers. Many institutions can exercise autonomy in many issues, but the Ministry of Education (Monbusho) keeps hold of the main influence over the growth and development of higher education in Japan.The higher education in Japan begins after the completion of 12 years of education comprising, 6 years of elementary education and 6 years of secondary education (lower and upper secondary schooling). The students graduating from High school are eligible to go for higher education in Japan.  Around 45% students from high school opt for higher education.</string>
    <string name="ChinaHome">The Mandarin Language Teaching Program, or MALTEP, aims to develop and implement Mandarin language programs for Indian students. MALTEP is a part of our effort to support the study of China in India.The program will place five Mandarin language instructors at top Indian universities and business schools over the next three years. These instructors will develop and implement Mandarin teaching programs for host universities in India for a period of two years. The program will provide two years of Mandarin study to undergraduate and graduate students, the first year of which will build foundational written and verbal capacity in the language. The second is customizable – universities could offer Mandarin courses tailored to the needs of specific disciplines and industries.The Mandarin Language Scholars Program is an opportunity for young Indian scholars and practitioners to develop a working knowledge of the Mandarin language for research, teaching, or professional work, through one-year intensive Mandarin Language training in Taiwan.A fully funded program, the fellowship is open to applicants from different backgrounds-academia, research, or practitioners. The applicant must have a proven record of working with or on China. For instance, scholars applying to the fellowship should either be pursuing their Masters’ or PhD in China Studies (or an associated field) or have finished their PhDs no earlier than 2016. Practitioners who work in a field with a specific focus on China can also apply.</string>
</resources>